<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[test]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[test]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:17:20 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TASTE Summit - Executive Day]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>TASTE Summit - Executive Day</h1>,<h2>Are you interested in new insights in Gastronomy? Do you want to know everything about the latest international developments on flavor and tasting ánd broaden your network at the same time? Then you should join this year’s TASTE Summit – Executive day!

On Wednesday the 12th of July, specialists and industry leaders from all over the world come together at the Hotel Management School Maastricht to share their vision on the importance of flavor and tasting in their organizations. We offer a unique program of speakers who will all underline the importance of food – especially deliciousness and liking – to them and you!

Our speakers include:
-	Michiel Bakker (Global director of Google Food)
-	Prof. Charles Spence (Oxford University)
-	Paul Pairet (Ultraviolet – Shanghai)
-	Sara Roversi & Nick Difino (Future Food Insitute – Bologna)
-	Milan Arandelovic (Hilton)
-	Charles van Goch (Mise en Place)
-	Dr. Peter Klosse (Hotel Management School Maastricht)
Presented by Hans Steenbergen (Food Inspiration)

For an even more unforgettable experience, there’s the opportunity to go on an exclusive field-trip the next morning (Thursday 13th of July). On this trip we will visit Rungis (the largest food market in the world, located in Paris) followed by a lunch at Moët & Chandon in Epernay. 
	
The Executive Day is open to public and offers a great chance to get exclusive insights in the industry and broaden your network. Get your tickets now and BE THERE!

Date: 12th of July 2017
Time: 09:00 – 17:00
Location: Hotel Management School Maastricht, The Netherlands
Costs: € 275,- (including gastronomic lunch)
Including Field trip: € 525,-

More info >>
www.taste-summit.com
organization@taste-summit.com

Get your tickets here >>
http://bit.ly/TASTE-tickets</h2>,<article><img src="https://scontent.xx.fbcdn.net/v/t31.0-8/c653.0.720.720/p720x720/18451780_865789746901403_5892616918336142738_o.jpg?oh=4fbd548b4345b0dcababae5496f0fb44&oe=59E9DF6B"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/taste-summit-executive-day/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6f66dbf5-3695-49ec-9153-156d897a5311</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:16:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>