<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[test]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[test]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:30:10 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:30:03 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TASTE Summit]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>TASTE Summit</h1>,<p>Another one of our keynote speakers at the TASTE Summit – Executive Day will be Prof. Charles Spence. Prof. Charles Spence is an experimental psychologist at the University of Oxford. He is the head of the cross-modal Research group which specializes in the research on integration of information across different sensory modalities. Spence is also a consultant for a number of multinational companies advising on various aspects of multi-sensory design. He currently works on problems associated with design of foods that maximally stimulate the senses, and the effect of the indoor environment on mood, well-being, and performance. During our Executive Day, Prof. Charles Spence will discuss multi-sensory food – “food is more than just ingredients” More info &gt;&gt; www.taste-summit.com organization@taste-summit.com Tickets &gt;&gt; http://bit.ly/TASTE-tickets</p>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/e23e14abb813db3d84590ff2d82bce38/noop.jpg?input=https%3A%2F%2Fscontent.xx.fbcdn.net%2Fv%2Ft1.0-9%2Fs720x720%2F18622617_869138996566478_8534119402973621632_n.jpg%3Foh%3D5b72a3649d549b84c32af818bc4dbec1%26oe%3D59A97E4A">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/taste-summit/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">b5da33eb-4599-4f48-a313-af40db0a4dbf</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Charles van Goch]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Charles van Goch</h1>,<p>Charles van Goch will also be joining us at the TASTE Summit – Executive Day! Charles van Goch is a Hotel Management School Maastricht graduate and the founder of Mise en Place. Mise en Place is an international leading employment agency specialized in the hospitality trade since 1994 and to be found in 7 countries with 55 offices. Van Goch is one large chunk of energy and he loves to share that energy with people. He gets his energy from talking to people, motivating and inspiring them. We can't wait to be inspired by him on Wednesday the 12th of July! More info &gt;&gt; www.facebook.com/events/1568821833135394 www.taste-summit.com organization@taste-summit.com Tickets &gt;&gt; http://bit.ly/TASTE-tickets</p>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/e4dc961a734b4cc0d80de9c3efca0e246314bba9.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/taste-summit/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">30d6ce70-3322-4eeb-9781-075132cd90db</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:16:56 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TASTE Summit]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>TASTE Summit</h1>,<p>We are proud to have Michiel Bakker as one of our keynote speakers at the TASTE Summit – Executive Day! As Google’s Director of Global Food Services, Michiel Bakker oversees Google’s Global Food program. Michiel and his team take pride in fueling the minds and bodies of those behind Google’s innovative products, serving over 165,000 delicious, nutritious and responsibly sourced meals in 56 countries, around the world, each day. Through great food experiences, Google Food fosters culture, collaboration and innovation at work. As the leader of the program, Michiel is focused on developing new insights and evidence on how food experiences can enable individuals and teams to be at their best – short and long term – and developing internal and external global partnerships to explore and tackle the challenges and opportunities in the broader food systems. The team is also actively working on promoting plant forward diets and enabling individuals to make personal, informed food choices for sustainable lifestyles. During our Executive Day, Michiel Bakker will speak about “The Googler’s approach” More info &gt;&gt; www.taste-summit.com organization@taste-summit.com Tickets &gt;&gt; http://bit.ly/TASTE-tickets</p>,<img src="https://imgflo.herokuapp.com/graph/2b2431f8e7ba7b0/f5e84a41e78bcbbed394069c4959e820/noop.jpg?input=https%3A%2F%2Fscontent.xx.fbcdn.net%2Fv%2Ft1.0-9%2Fp720x720%2F18620389_868472326633145_940950048163348259_n.jpg%3Foh%3D62901507d40b97ab4ac2ae144f839042%26oe%3D59BBEA36">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/taste-summit/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">393f5f77-a6ca-4cb8-b78e-e07e70ff37e0</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:16:52 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[TASTE Summit - Executive Day]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h3>TASTE Summit - Executive Day</h3>,<p>Are you interested in new insights in Gastronomy? Do you want to know everything about the latest international developments on flavor and tasting ánd broaden your network at the same time? Then you should join this year’s TASTE Summit – Executive day! On Wednesday the 12th of July, specialists and industry leaders from all over the world come together at the Hotel Management School Maastricht to share their vision on the importance of flavor and tasting in their organizations. We offer a unique program of speakers who will all underline the importance of food – especially deliciousness and liking – to them and you! Our speakers include: - Michiel Bakker (Global director of Google Food) - Prof. Charles Spence (Oxford University) - Paul Pairet (Ultraviolet – Shanghai) - Sara Roversi &amp; Nick Difino (Future Food Insitute – Bologna) - Milan Arandelovic (Hilton) - Charles van Goch (Mise en Place) - Dr. Peter Klosse (Hotel Management School Maastricht) Presented by Hans Steenbergen (Food Inspiration) For an even more unforgettable experience, there’s the opportunity to go on an exclusive field-trip the next morning (Thursday 13th of July). On this trip we will visit Rungis (the largest food market in the world, located in Paris) followed by a lunch at Moët &amp; Chandon in Epernay. The Executive Day is open to public and offers a great chance to get exclusive insights in the industry and broaden your network. Get your tickets now and BE THERE! Date: 12th of July 2017 Time: 09:00 – 17:00 Location: Hotel Management School Maastricht, The Netherlands Costs: € 275,- (including gastronomic lunch) Including Field trip: € 525,- More info &gt;&gt; www.taste-summit.com organization@taste-summit.com Get your tickets here &gt;&gt; http://bit.ly/TASTE-tickets</p>,<img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/ef883694886020ddeac42baf28070006d72560d6.jpg" title="TASTE Summit Executive Day">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/harpert-v1/taste-summit-executive-day/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6f66dbf5-3695-49ec-9153-156d897a5311</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2017 20:16:46 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>